<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Islash8</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Islash8</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Islash8</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 01:39:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Covid_Thoughts1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/covid_thoughts1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Apr 2023 01:39:29 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/covid_thoughts1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title> الأقرع والأبرص والأعمى!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/%D8%AD%D8%AF%D9%8A%D8%AB%D9%A2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 16:37:45 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/%D8%AD%D8%AF%D9%8A%D8%AB%D9%A2/</guid>
      <description>نتناول اليوم حديث جديد عن أبي هريرة رضي الله عنه أنه سمع النبي صلى الله عليه وسلم ، يقول: &amp;ldquo;إنّ ثلاثة من بني إسرائيل: أبرص وأقرع وأعمى، فأراد الله أن يَبْتَلِيَهم، فبعث إليهم ملَكًا، فأتى الأبرص؛ فقال: أيُّ شيء أحب إليك؟ قال: لون حسن، وجلد حسن، ويذهب عني الذي قد قَذِرَني النَّاس به. قال: فمسحه فذهب عنه قَذَرُه، فأُعْطِيَ لوناً حسناً وجلداً حسناً. قال: فأي المال أحب إليك؟ قال: الإبل أو البقر -شك إسحاق-.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>أبى ذرع؟!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/%D8%AD%D8%AF%D9%8A%D8%AB%D9%A1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 16:37:45 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/%D8%AD%D8%AF%D9%8A%D8%AB%D9%A1/</guid>
      <description>أصدقائي! اليوم سنتحدث عن حديث أبي ذرع لنتاول ما به من بلاغة وفصاحة اللغة العربية. يتناول هذا الحديث قصة عشر نساء اجتمعن واتفقن على أن يتحدثن بصدق عن أزواجهن.&#xA;نص الحديث: &amp;quot; عَن عَائِشَةَ - رَضِيَ اللَّهُ عَنهَا - قَالَت: &amp;quot;جلست إحدى عشر امرأة، فتعاهَدنَ وتعاقدن أن لا يكتمن من أخبار أزواجهن شيئاً.&#xA;(فقالت الأولى): زوجي لحم جَملٍ, غَثّ، على رأس جبل وعر، لا سهلٌ فيرتقى، ولا سمينٌ فينتقل.&#xA;(قالت الثانية): زوجي لا أثير خبره، إني أخاف أن لا أذَرَهُ، إن أذكره أذكر عُجَره وبُجَره.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The creation of a blog!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/creatingblog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 21:47:01 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/creatingblog/</guid>
      <description>This is a tutorial about how this thing is done maybe it would be useful for someone.&#xA;Quick Introduction&#xA;Hugo is a fast and flexible static site generator, perfect for building blogs and websites. When paired with GitHub Pages, it becomes even more powerful, enabling easy version control and free hosting. In this guide, we will walk through the process of creating a blog using Hugo and deploying it on GitHub Pages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello ... AGAIN</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/new_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 20:53:26 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/new_post/</guid>
      <description>Greetings, Internet!&#xA;This is my third attempt at writing my first blog post, and hopefully, this time, I can maintain it!&#xA;Life has been quite busy over the past few years. A lot has happened—exciting if you&amp;rsquo;re someone who loves action and unpredictability! However, for me, it has been nothing short of a rollercoaster.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;ve been experimenting with Hugo and blogs for almost five years now, but I still don&amp;rsquo;t feel like I&amp;rsquo;ve truly mastered it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I am the Muffin man!&#xA;The Muffin man?&#xA;THE MUFFIN MAN!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>This is a place holder page acts as a contact page for the audiance trying to reach yours truly.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
